Warren S. McCulloch Papers 1860s-1987 Mss.B.M139
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1931-1968; 13.5 lin. feet (Box 1-28)
  - Liberman, E. James, 1960; 1 item
  - Liberson, W. T., 1947-1952; 7 items
  - Lichtblau, Newton S., n.d.; 1 item
  - Lichtenstein, Ben W., 1947; 1 item
  - Liddell, H. S., 1948-1949; 4 items
  - Lieberman, E. James, 1960; 1 item
  - Lillie, Ralph S., 1943; 2 items
  - Lilly, John C., 1951-1966; 4 items
  - Lincoln (Mass.) Public Schools, 1966-1967; 2 items
  - Lindahl, Leslie E. H., 1959; 2 items
  - Lindberg, Donald A. B., 1965; 2 items
  - Linn, Louis, 1950; 2 items
  - Linwood, Walter E., 1954; 2 items
  - Lipetz, Leo E., 1962-1969; 15 items
  - Lipkin, Mack, 1948-1950; 5 items
  - Lipkin, Mickey, 1969; 1 item
  - Lipton, Barbara, 1948; 3 items
  - Lipton, Morris, 1947; 1 item
  - Liss, Donald, 1964-1965; 5 items
  - Lister, William C., 1954-1955; 11 item
  - Litchfield, Edward H., 1957; 1 item
  - Lith, Paul van, 1967; 3 items
  - Little, Brown and Co.: Bartlett's Familar Quotations, 1958-1963; 5 items
  - Littlejohn, S. Bernard, 1950; 1 item
  - Livingston, Robert B., 1949-1951; 7 items
  - Livingston, William K., 1947-1954; 20 items
  - Lloyd, David, 1940-1950; 10 items
  - Lockard, Isabel, 1952-1953; 2 items
  - Locke, W. N., 1956; 1 item
  - Loeb, Arthur L., 1958; 1 item
  - Loeb, Mrs. Lottie (Arthur L), 1968; 1 item
  - Lofgren, Lars, 1964-1965; 2 items
  - Lohse, Henry W., 1950; 5 items
  - Longview State Hospital (Ohio), 1961; 1 item
  - Longyear, Christopher R., 1968-1969; 7 items
  - Loonstra, F., 1968; 2 items
  - Lorente de Nó R., 1944-21950; 8 items
  - Lorz, Helen, 1953; 2 items
  - Lovins, Amory B., 1968; 1 item
  - Lowenbach, Hans, 1948; 2 items
  - Lowenstein, O. E., 1953; 1 item
  - Lowry, Romny H., 1962; 1 item
  - Loyola University. School of Medicine, 1945; 2 items
  - Lu, Frank C., 1951; 4 items
  - Lucas, H. L., 1962; 2 items
  - Luce, R. H., 1961; 4 items
  - Ludwin, J., 1964; 1 item
  - Luebke, Eugene C., 1951; 2 items
  - Lundberg, Anders, 1950; 2 items
  - Lunt, William E., 1952; 1 item
  - Lustman, Claire R., 1957; 1 item
  - Lyman, John, 1958-1959; 4 items
  - Lysergic Acid, 1950; 1 item
  - McCammon, Charles J., 1947; 2 items
  - McCaslin, Murray F., 1957; 1 item
  - McCloskey, Chester M., 1960; 1 item
  - McCool, Dick C., 1951; 2 items
  - McCouch, Grayson P., 1950-1953; 4 items
  - Mc Cowan, P. K., 1950-1951; 3 items
  - McCoy, A. D., 1953; 2 items
  - McCulloch, David Sears, 1951-1961; 3 items
  - McCulloch, Mary, 1947-1951; 3 items
  - McCulloch, Margaret, 1949; 5 items
  - McCulloch, Mary, 1952; 1 item
  - McCulloch, Paul, 1948-1952; 7 items
  - McCulloch, Warren Sturgis. Ciriculum vitae, 1951-1952; 6 items
  - McCulloch, 65th Anniversary Letters, 1968-1970; 9 items
  - McCulloch, Book Reviews, 1966-1967; 2 items
  - MacDonald, John S., 1963; 1 item
  - MacDonald, L. W., 1955; 1 item
  - MacFadyen, Douglas A., 1959; 2 items
  - McHale, Katherine, 1954; 1 item
  - MacInnes, D. A., 1943; 1 item
  - Mace, C. A., 1955-1964; 2 items
  - Mace, Robert, 1965; 1 item
  - McEachern, Donald, 1948; 3 items
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc., 1950-1969; 7 items
  - Machol, Robert E., 1962-1967; 8 items
  - MacIntosh, Archibald, 1968; 1 item
  - MacKay, Donald M., 1950-1969; 84 items
  - MacKay, Roland P., 1947-1951; 3 items
  - McLardy, Turner, 1949-1964; 43 items
  - Maclean, John, 1953; 1 item
  - MacLean, Paul D., 1952-1963; 14 items
  - McNarry, L. R., 1969; 2 items
  - MacNeal, Edward, 1948; 1 item
  - MacPhee, Allan, 1967; 3 items
  - McQueen, J. D., 1946-1954; 6 items
  - Madow, William, 1949-1950; 11 item
  - Madsen, Annelise, 1951; 1 item
  - Magladery, J. W., 1948-1949; 9 items
  - Magnes, Jonathan, 1950; 3 items
  - Magnus, O., 1949-1961; 16 items
  - Magoun, H. W., 1950-1960; 9 items
  - Maier, Franz, 1960; 1 item
  - Maison, George L., n.d.; 1 item
  - Maitra, K. K, 1960; 14 items
  - Malcolm, L., 1958; 2 items
  - Malcolm, S. L., 1958; 1 item
  - Malik, Rex, 1965-1968; 8 items
  - Mallinckrodt Chemicals, 1947; 4 items
  - Manghi, Ernesto, 1958-1959; 2 items
  - Mann, William C., 1961; 1 item
  - Mapes, Milton C., Jr., 1966; 2 items
  - Marill, Thomas, 1963; 1 item
  - Mark, Richard, 1966; 2 items
  - Maron, M. E., 1962-1969; 14 items
  - Marrazzi, Amedeo S., 1952-1963; 5 items
  - Mars, Louis, 1947-1964; 5 items
  - Marsden, Keith, 1968; 1 item
  - Marshall, Byron O., 1953; 1 item
  - Marshall, Curtis, 1952; 2 items
  - Marshall, Wade H., 1948-1954; 3 items
  - Martin, Deac, 1954; 1 item
  - Martin, W. T., 1965; 2 items
  - Martin, Wagner Waneck, 1967; 10 items
  - Maruyama, Magoroh, 1956-1960; 10 items
  - Masland, Richard L., 1950-1951; 3 items
  - Mason, Herman C., 1954-1956; 2 items
  - Massachusetts. Industrial Liaison Office, 1961-1969; 4 items
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1952; 2 items
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Press, 1968-1969; 3 items
  - Masserman, Jules H., 1954; 1 item
  - Matarazzo, Salvatora, 1966; 1 item
  - Matthews, Sir Bryan, 1955; 3 items
  - Matthysse, Steven W., 1966; 5 items
  - Mawe, Richard C., 1966; 1 item
  - May, Kenneth O., 1952; 2 items
  - Mayer-Gross, William, 1947-1951; 18 items
  - Mayer, Stephan, 1955-1962; 13 items
  - Mayne, Robert, 1955; 3 items
  - Mayo, Alfred, 1958; 1 item
  - Mead, Margaret, 1945; 1 item
  - Medem, Federico, to Harvey Savely, 1966; 2 items
  - Medical Bureau, 1952; 2 items
  - Medical Center Commission. Chicago, 1949; 3 items
  - Medical College of Virginia, 1965-1966; 3 items
  - Meduna, Ladislas J., 1947-1956; 5 items
  - Meharry Medical College, 1968; 2 items
  - Meier, Rolf, 1949; 6 items
  - Meijler, Frits L., 1967; 1 item
  - Meister, Ralph K., 1949-1959; 13 items
  - Melaned, June, 1951; 2 items
  - Mendell, Herman, 1963; 1 item
  - Menger, Karl, 1946-1960; 11 item
  - Mercer, William Ralph, 1967; 2 items
  - Merck and Co., 1946-1947; 10 items
  - Meredith, G. Patrick, 1966-1969; 18 items
  - Merrill, R. G., 1962; 1 item
  - Merritt, H. Houston, 1942-1951; 5 items
  - Methodist Church. Board of Education, 1966; 2 items
  - Methodos, 1956; 1 item
  - Metzelaar, Paul N., 1958; 1 item
  - Meyer, A., 1949; 3 items
  - Meyers, Ernest, 1954; 3 items
  - Meyers, Russell, 1956-1963; 20 items
  - Middlebury College, 1955; 2 items
  - Mildrum Louis, 1959-1962; 3 items
  - Miles, Walter, 1949-1954; 2 items
  - Miller, Frederick R., 1948-1950; 3 items
  - Miller, George A., 1949-1957; 4 items
  - Miller, Glenn, 1963; 1 item
  - Miller, Neal E., 1949; 4 items
  - Miller, Raymond N., 1949; 2 items
  - Milwaukee Neuropsychiatric Society, 1947; 1 item
  - Minot, Otis N., 1964-198; 2 items
  - Minsky, Gloria A. Rudisch, 1967-1968; 3 items
  - Mira, Pepe, 1968; 1 item
  - Mirsky, I. Arthur, 1950; 2 items
  - Mitchell, H. H, 1954; 1 item
  - Mittelmann, Eugene, 1960; 1 item
  - Mochizuki, Masaji, 1950; 3 items
  - Modular Electronics, Inc., 1964; 1 item
  - Moeller, Becky, n.d.; 1 item
  - Moffett, James, 1963; 2 items
  - Mohler, William C., 1948; 3 items
  - Moles, A., 1959; 1 item
  - Montague, Ashley, 1959; 5 items
  - Montgomery, E. B., 1963; 1 item
  - Montgomery, Merlin Walter, 1969; 3 items
  - Montreal, Neurological Institute, 1963; 2 items
  - Mooers, Calvin N., 1966; 6 items
  - Mooradian, Karlen, 1966; 3 items
  - Moore, Glenn H., 1951; 1 item
  - Moore, John N., 1955; 1 item
  - Moore, Merrill, 1953; 3 items
  - Moore, Thomas, 1963-1965; 4 items
  - Moore, W. Cullen, 1949-1955; 9 items
  - Morales, Manuel, 1967; 4 items
  - Morchio, Rouzo, 1957; 1 item
  - Moreno, J. L., 1956; 1 item
  - Moreno-Diaz, Roberto, 1967-1969; 10 items
  - Morgan, Clifford T., 1947-1950; 7 items
  - Morgan, Marus, 1949-1952; 12 items
  - Morgan, Richard, 1950; 2 items
  - Morgane, P. J., 1956; 1 item
  - Morgenstein, Jacques, 1966; 6 items
  - Morin, G., 1951; 2 items
  - Morison, Robert S., 1947-1950; 15 items
  - Morrell, Frank, 1965; 1 item
  - Morris, Arthur A., 1950; 2 items
  - Morris, Charles, 1946; 1 item
  - Morris, William E., 1951; 3 items
  - Morsden, Keith, 1967; 1 item
  - Morse, Lew H., 1949; 2 items
  - Moruzzie, Giuseppe, 1951-1965; 6 items
  - Mosberg, William H., Jr., 1950-1956; 11 item
  - Moses, Lincoln E., 1965; 1 item
  - Moss, Mary M., 1949; 2 items
  - Mount-Castle, A. C., 1953; 1 item
  - Mountcastle, Vernon B., 1958-1959; 4 items
  - Moursund, Walter, 1950; 4 items
  - Muller, Peter, 1962; 2 items
  - Mullin, Albert A., 1959-1961; 2 items
  - Munson, John H., n.d.; 1 item
  - Muntyan, 1949; 1 item
  - Muntz, William, 1967; 1 item
  - Murphy, A. L., 1949; 1 item
  - Murphy, J. L., 1964; 1 item
  - Murphy, J. P., 1948-1967; 5 items
  - Muses, Charles A., 1960-1968; 17 items
  - Nachmansohn, David, 1943-1952; 3 items
  - Nakagawa, Hidezo, 1950; 2 items
  - Napolkov, A. V., 1965; 4 items
  - Naquet, Robert, n.d.; 1 item
  - Nash, Claude, 1967; 1 item
  - Natapoff, Alan, 1963; 1 item
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1955; 3 items
  - National Biomedical Research Foundation, 1960; 2 items
  - National Film Board of Canada, 1960-1962; 6 items
  - National Institute of General Medical Sciences, 1967; 1 item
  - National Research Council, 1947-1952; 20 items
  - National Paraplegia Foundation, 1955; 1 item
  - National Science Foundation, 1953-1967; 9 items
  - National Society of Crippled Children and Adults, Inc., 1951; 2 items
  - Nauta, Walle J. H., 1963-1968; 3 items
  - Neale, Claude L., 1949; 3 items
  - Nelson, Arthur A., 1948; 1 item
  - Nemiah, J.C., 1948; 1 items
  - Neurological Science Research Training Committee, 1968; 2 items
  - Neurology, 1953; 5 items
  - Neurosciences Research Program, 1966; 1 item
  - New Jersey Neuropsychiatiric Assoc., 1956; 1 item
  - New York Academy of the Sciences, 1958-1967; 5 items
  - New York University. College of Engineering, 1963; 2 items
  - New York University. School of Medicine, 1963-1965; 6 items
  - New York State Univ, Library., 1968; 1 item
  - New York Times, 1964; 1 item
  - Newberry Library, 1949; 1 item
  - Newland, T. Ernest, 1951; 10 items
  - Newsday, 1957; 1 item
  - Newsome, Julie, 1969; 1 item
  - Newsome and Company, 1969; 1 item
  - Newsweek, 1949; 1 item
  - Niederer, Gertrude A., 1959; 4 items
  - Nielson, Paul E., 1950; 2 items
  - Nims, Leslie F., 1942-1947; 4 items
  - Nobel, Martha, 1952; 3 items
  - Noell, Werner K., 1956-1968; 3 items
  - Nolan, William J., 1951; 2 items
  - Norman, Harold, 1947; 1 item
  - Northrop, Filmer S. C., 1930-1968; 42 items
  - Northwest Congress of Optomerty, 1951; 3 items
  - Northwestern University, 1949-1950; 2 items
  - Notley, M. G., 1966; 1 item
  - Nowels, Anthony, 1964; 1 item
  - Noyes, Edward S., 1948; 2 items
  - Nu Sigma Nu, 1950; 1 item
  - Nulsen, Frank E., 1948; 4 items
  - Nyabongo, Akiki K., 1946; 1 item
  - Oberlander, E. B., 1954; 2 items
  - Oestreicher, Hans L., 1965-1966; 7 items
  - Oetting, Robert F., 1950; 1 item
  - Offenhauser, William H., 1966; 2 items
  - Offner, Franklin F., 1983-1966; 6 items
  - Ogata, Tomio, 1950; 2 items
  - Ogawa, Teizo, 1950; 2 items
  - Ogle, Kenneth, 1956; 2 items
  - Oldberg, Eric, 1943; 2 items
  - O'Leary, James L., 1945; 1 item
  - Oliver, Wade W., 1953; 1 item
  - Olney, John C., 1965; 2 items
  - Olsen, Norman S., 1947-1950; 7 items
  - Olson, D. E., 1948; 1 item
  - Olson, Ralph A., 1952; 1 item
  - Olson, Stanley W., 1950-1952; 10 items
  - Onesto, Nello M., 1959-1965; 14 items
  - Onsager, Lars, 1968; 2 items
  - Ontario Psychiatric Assoc., 1957; 1 item
  - Operations Research Society of America, 32nd National Meeting, 1967; 3 items
  - Oppenheim, Paul, 1958; 1 item
  - Oppenheimer, Ernst, 1946-1949; 6 items
  - Oppenheimer, Jane M., 1955; 2 items
  - Organon, Inc., 1949; 3 items
  - Orione, Julio, 1950; 1 item
  - Ortega, Luis, 1949; 2 items
  - Oser, Peter, 1963-1967; 7 items
  - Osmundsen, John A., 1963; 2 items
  - Ott, David Ekern, 1962; 25 items
  - Overhage, Carl F. J., 1959; 1 item
  - Padalino, Francesco, 1950; 7 items
  - Paddock, Ruth T., 1954; 1 item
  - Page, Thornton, 1950; 8 items
  - Pain, R. H., 1959; 2 items
  - Paloczi-Horvath, George, 1963-1964; 4 items
  - Panpiglione, G., 1954; 1 item
  - Panasewicz, J., 1964; 7 items
  - Pantaleo, Mario, 1967; 3 items
  - Papikonomou, E., 1968; 3 items
  - Papert, Seymour, 1961-1964; 20 items
  - Paranoids, 1950-1951; 6 items
  - Pardee, Harvey S., 1949; 5 items
  - Park, Walter F., 1963; 1 item
  - Parker, Eugene A., 1954; 1 item
  - Parker-Rhoades, Frederick, 1964; 2 items
  - Pascual-Leone, Juan, 1968; 2 items
  - Pask, A. Gordon, 1959-1968; 40 items
  - Pathfinder, 1947; 3 items
  - Patry, Frederick L., 1961; 2 items
  - Pattishall, Evan G., 1956; 2 items
  - Patton, H. D., 1951; 1 item
  - Pawelski, Joan, 1959; 3 items
  - Payne, Buryl, 1967; 2 items
  - Payson, Charles Shipman, 1968-1969; 4 items
  - Paxson, Edward W., 1965; 3 items
  - Peacock, Samuel M., Jr., 1951-1953; 8 items
  - Pease, Craig S., 1961; 6 items
  - Pedelty, Michael, 1959-1969; 24 items
  - Peirce, Charles S., 1961-1964; 6 items
  - Penfield, Wilder, 1947-1965; 20 items
  - Pennsylvania. Department of Welfare, 1948-1950; 22 items
  - Penrose, L., 1961; 1 item
  - Penrose, Roger, 1958; 2 items
  - Pergamon Press, Inc, 1959; 8 items
  - Perkins, W. J., 1959-1961; 2 items
  - Perl, Menachem, 1965; 5 items
  - Perlstein, M. A., 1951; 3 items
  - Perlzweig, William, 1948; 1 item
  - Perot, Phanor L., Jr., 1951-1965; 13 items
  - Perry, Sheridan L. C., 1953-1954; 4 items
  - Perryman, James H., 1948; 2 items
  - Perryman, Mrs. Verne B., 1945-1958; 77 items
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine, 1960-1961; 6 items
  - Pescatori, Alberto, 19611962; 5 items
  - Peters, Charlotte H., 1945; 2 items
  - Peters, Helen, 1966; 1 item
  - Peters, Joseph J., 1954-1959; 2 items
  - Peters, Walter F., 1952; 1 item
  - Petersen, W. F., 1942; 2 items
  - Peterson, Axel H., 1955-1956; 3 items
  - Peterson, Eric W., 1948-1950; 9 items
  - Petri, Carl Adam, 1962; 2 items
  - Petrie, Asenath, 1949-1955; 11 item
  - Pfeiffer, Andrew, 7 items
  - Pfeiffer, Carl C., 1952-1958; 3 items
  - Pfeiffer, John E., 1946-1965; 36 items
  - Phi Rho Sigma, 1949; 1 item
  - Philco Corp., 1961; 2 items
  - Phillips, Charles G., 1959; 2 items
  - Phillips, Peter, 1956; 5 items
  - Philosophy of Science Association, 1950; 2 items
  - Phipps and Bird, Inc., 1947; 1 item
  - Physicians and Surgeons Quarterly, 1969; 1 item
  - Physics Today, 1951; 4 items
  - Piaget, Jean, 1953-1964; 27 items
  - Pickard, William F., 1966-1968; 13 items
  - Pickett, Clarence E., 1946; 1 item
  - Pickford, Mary, 1949-1950; 2 items
  - Pierce, William A., 1962; 5 items
  - Pierson, Roger G., Jr., 1963; 2 items
  - Piggins, David J., 1968; 2 items
  - Pike, Eugene W., 1941-1967; 22 items
  - Pike, Frank Henry, 1939-1949; 55 items
  - Pikler, Andrew G., 1954-1967; 22 items
  - Pile, Wilson, 1961; 2 items
  - Pilgrim, A. J., 1962; 1 item
  - Pitesky, Isadore, 1950-1951; 3 items
  - Pitman-Moore Company, 1952; 1 item
  - Pitts, Walter, 1946-1969; 4 folders
  - Pleissner, Ella D., 1948; 1 item
  - Polissar, Milton J., 1949; 2 items
  - Pollock, Donald K., 1967; 3 items
  - Pollock, George H., 1947-1951; 5 items
  - Polonsky, J., 1959; 5 items
  - Polt, George, n.d.; 1 item
  - Pool, J. Lawrence, 1947; 1 item
  - Popular Mechanics, 1949; 1 item
  - Porter, A., 1959; 5 items
  - Portis, Sidney A., 1948; 4 items
  - Posluns, Don, 1959; 1 item
  - Postgraduate Center for Psychotheraphy, 1957; 1 item
  - Potter, V. R., 1945; 1 item
  - Pozo-Olano, Juan de Dios, 1967-1969; 113 items
  - Prepp, Kenneth, 1951; 1 item
  - Prescott, Holden, 1935-1963; 24 items
  - Preston, Frederick W., 1958; 1 item
  - Pribram, Karl H., 1966-1967; 4 items
  - Price, Albert, 1961; 1 item
  - Price, David E., 1949; 1 item
  - Proceedings of the Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1949; 2 items
  - Proctor, Charles D., 1950-1968; 13 items
  - Proctor, Lorne D., 1954-1967; 19 items
  - Proder, S., 1944; 2 items
  - Prosser, C. L., 1948-1949; 5 items
  - Psi Chi, 1949-1950; 4 items
  - Psychological Book Preveiws, 1951; 5 items
  - Psychology Today, 1967-1968; 8 items
  - Psychophysics Research Corp., 1963; 3 items
  - "Psychotic Letters", 1968; 2 items
  - Puharich, Henry K., 1950-1963; 20 items
  - Purdue University, 1964-1966; 4 items
  - Purdy, Donald M., 1958; 3 items
  - Putnam, Peter, 1964; 4 items
  - Putnam, Tracy J., 1940; 2 items
  - Quarrington, Bruce, 1953; 1 item
  - Quarterly Review of Biology, 1968; 4 items
  - Quastel, J. H., 1940-1941; 5 items
  - Quastler, Henry, 1951-1953; 12 items
  - Quimby, E. J., 1955; 2 items
  - Quimby, F. H., 1952-1953; 3 items
  - Quine, W. V., 1958; 1 item
  - Rabin, Harold, 1949; 1 item
  - Rabiner, A. M., 1956; 3 items
  - Rafferty, James A., 1950; 4 items
  - RAI -- Italian Radio TV System, 1967-1968; 4 items
  - Raines, George N., 1947-1949; 2 items
  - Ramsay, Diane M., 1967; 3 items
  - Rand Corporation, 1951-1962; 5 items
  - Radio Club of America, 1955; 1 item
  - Rail Travel Credit Agency, 1956; 2 items
  - Ramabhadaran, G. N. to Dr. Cerrillo, 1963; 1 item
  - Randolph, John F., 1962; 2 items
  - Ransmeier, R. E., 1949; 3 items
  - Ranson, S. W., 1941; 1 item
  - Rapisarda, Vittorio, 1964; 5 items
  - Rappapart, Irving, 1952; 2 items
  - Rashevsky, N., 1943-1964; 46 items
  - Ravdin, I. S., 1960; 1 item
  - Ratheon Company, 1960; 2 items
  - Read, Margaret Ruth, 1954-1960; 13 items
  - Reader's Digest, 1949-1954; 6 items
  - Redlich, F. C., 1948-1951; 11 item
  - Reed, Carlos I., 1952-1963; 8 items
  - Reed, Charles A., 1965; 3 items
  - Rees, Mina, 1951; 1 item
  - Reeve, E. B., 1967; 1 item
  - Reich, Herbert J., 1948; 2 items
  - Reichard, J. Davis, 1948-1952; 2 items
  - Reichart, Werner, 1968; 2 items
  - Reichbach, Juliusz, 1965; 1 item
  - Reichmann, Peter Ivan, 1966; 3 items
  - Reinstein, H. C., 1961-1964; 4 items
  - Reister, Philip, 1961; 2 items
  - Reiter, Harvey, 1952; 1 item
  - Reiter, Stanley, 1966; 1 item
  - Remond, Antoine, 1948-1969; 70 items
  - Renfrew, Alice G., 1947; 2 items
  - Renn, Charles E., 1960; 1 item
  - Resources for the Future, Inc., 1967; 3 items
  - Reynolds, Harriet, 1958; 2 items
  - Rhoads, C. P., 1946; 1 item
  - Ricciardi, Luigi M., 1967; 3 items
  - Rice, Arthur H., 1953; 2 items
  - Rice, S. O., 1949; 1 item
  - Richards, R. K., 1953-1954; 6 items
  - Richter, Derek, 1949; 1 item
  - Ridenour, Louis N., 1948-1950; 14 items
  - Ridley, Ellen, 1945-1950; 8 items
  - Riesen, Austin H., 1961; 1 item
  - Riess, Bill, 1957; 1 item
  - Rigas, Mrs Harriett, 1961; 2 items
  - Riggs, F. Behn, 1968; 1 item
  - Riggs, Lorrin A., 1962; 1 item
  - Rimland, Bernard, 1964-1965; 7 items
  - Rioch, David McKenzie, 1940-1967; 20 items
  - Rittwagen, Majorie, 1947; 2 items
  - Robard, S., 1949; 1 item
  - Roberts, 1954; 1 item
  - Roberts, T. D. M., 1950-1951; 3 items
  - Roberts, William H., 1959; 3 items
  - Roberts, William H., Jr., 1961; 3 items
  - Robertson, A. D. J., 1967; 2 items
  - Robie, Theodore R., 1952; 2 items
  - Robinson, Bryan W., 1959-1960; 8 items
  - Robinson, Herbert W., 1966; 2 items
  - Robinson, P. K., 1951; 2 items
  - Roche Laboratories, 1967; 2 items
  - Rochester, Nathaniel, 1953; 2 items
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1946-1951; 12 items
  - Rodger, T. Ferguson, 1949; 3 items
  - Rodnick, Eliot H., 1948; 4 items
  - Rome, Howard P., 1948; 1 item
  - Ronning, Ruth Linnea, 1948; 10 items
  - Roosevelt University, 1965; 2 items
  - Rorick, Huck, 1968; 3 items
  - Rosborough, Pearl M., 1962-1968; 5 items
  - Rose, Augustus S., 1949; 3 items
  - Rose, Jerzy, 1949; 1 item
  - Roseman, Ephraim, 1940-1947; 20 items
  - Rosen, Robert, 1961-1966; 3 items
  - Rosenbaum, R. A., 1962; 1 item
  - Rosenberg, Arthur J., 1961; 1 item
  - Rosenberg, Barnett, 1966; 1 item
  - Rosenberg, Jerry M., 1967; 2 items
  - Rosenblatt, Frank, 1958-1962; 6 items
  - Rosenblith, Walter A., 1954; 1 item
  - Rosenbloom, Marian, 1951-1952; 2 items
  - Rosenblueth, Arthro, 1939-1948; 22 items
  - Rosenfeld, Azriel, 1966; 1 item
  - Rosenthal, Jerome A., 1964; 2 items
  - Rosenthal, Kurt, 1962; 1 item
  - Rosenthal, Sol Roy, 1962; 2 items
  - Rosner, Albert A., 1961; 2 items
  - Rosner, Burton S., 1952; 3 items
  - Ross, Ira S., 1959; 2 items
  - Ross, Robert E., 1968; 2 items
  - Ross, Thomas, 1949; 5 items
  - Ross-Duggan, John Kimbell, II, 1951-1954; 23 items
  - Rossen, Ralph, 1953; 1 item
  - Rotermund, Manfred, 1964; 1 item
  - Roth, Sidney G., 1960; 4 items
  - Rothschild, F. S., 1964; 1 item
  - Rothstein, Jerome, 1963-1967; 3 items
  - Roundtree, Donald W., 1949-1950; 4 items
  - Rowland, Stanley, 1949-1950; 4 items
  - Ryder, J. D., 1949-1952; 2 items
  - Rubio, Francisco, 1954; 2 items
  - Rue, Ruth E., 1954; 2 items
  - Ruesch, Jurgen, 1961-1967; 3 items
  - Ruff, Willie, 1972-77, n.d.; 4 items
  - Rush, Stanley, 1957; 1 item
  - Rushton, William A. H., 1959; 3 items
  - Russell, W. M. S., 1955; 1 item
  - Sachs, Ernest, Jr., 1947-1948; 4 items
  - Sager, O.G., 1936-1966; 20 items
  - Sakalosky, George P., 1967; 5 items
  - Samter, Max, 1950; 2 items
  - Samuel, Arthur L., 1959; 1 item
  - Sanbunsky, S., 1963; 1 item
  - Sandia Corporation, 1 item
  - Sandow, Alexander, 1946-1947; 6 items
  - Sandoz Chemical Works, Inc., 1947; 1 item
  - Sangster, M., 1956; 2 items
  - de Santellana, Giorgio, 1959-1963; 3 items
  - Santesmases, J. Garcia, n.d.; 1 item
  - Sargant, William, 1952-1957; 6 items
  - Sargent, Porter, 1946-1950; 7 items
  - Sarnoff, David, 1966; 2 items
  - Sato, Kensuke, 1949-1957; 9 items
  - Saunders, Marion, 1948; 1 item
  - Savage, L. James, 1953-1955; 4 items
  - Saxl, Hedwig, 1963; 2 items
  - Sayers, R. A., 1958; 1 item
  - Schaeffer, Cornelia, 1961-1965; 18 items
  - Schachter, Ruth, n.d.; 1 item
  - Schaffel, Joseph E., 1949; 2 items
  - Schaltenbrand, Georges, 1960; 5 items
  - Scheibel, Arnold B., 1949-1967; 72 items
  - Scher, Jordan M., 1952-1959; 6 items
  - Scherrer, Jean, 1948-1949; 5 items
  - Schief, A., 1966-1968; 2 items
  - Schilder Society, 1953; 1 item
  - Schlecht, William G., 1950; 4 items
  - Schmidhofer, Ernst, 1958-1959; 2 items
  - Schmidt, Carl F., 1943; 2 items
  - Schmidt, Robert H., 1962; 3 items
  - Schmitt, Otto H., 1950; 1 item
  - Schnabel, Carl, 1965-1966; 16 items
  - Schneider, Dietrich, 1964; 1 item
  - Schouten, J. F., 1948-1969; 9 items
  - Schuetzman, Herbert, 1950-1957; 4 items
  - Schutzenberger, Marco P., 1962-1967; 12 items
  - Schwab, Robert S., 1949-1951; 8 items
  - Schwartz, Henry G., 1947; 1 item
  - Science, 1962-1963; 5 items
  - Science. Reviews by W. S. McCulloch, 1963; 6 items
  - Science and Technology, 1963-1969; 6 items
  - Science Service, 1946-1960; 7 items
  - Scientific American, 1949; 3 items
  - Scientific Library Service, 1961; 2 items
  - Scientific Monthly, 1950; 2 items
  - Scientific Research, 1967; 3 items
  - Scott, Robert J., 1959-1961; 4 items
  - Scott, Thomas R., 1957-1958; 2 items
  - Scoville, William Beecher, 1948-1950; 3 items
  - Scully, Mrs. C., 1967; 2 items
  - Seale, W. Holt, 1955; 1 item
  - Search, John, 1947; 4 items
  - Searle and Co., 1950; 1 item
  - Segundo, Jose, P., 1952; 5 items
  - Seipel, John H., 1965; 3 items
  - Seitz, Fred, 1949; 1 item
  - Seitz, J. Russell M., 1966-1968; 8 items
  - Selfridge, Oliver, 1948; 1 item
  - Selling, Ben, 1967; 1 item
  - Selling, Lowell S., 1954; 1 item
  - Selye, Hans, 1950; 2 items
  - Sem-Jacobsen, Carl Wilhelm, 1959-1960; 3 items
  - Semon, Warren, 1963; 1 item
  - Serrano, Jaun Andres Agapito, 1967; 1 item
  - Service de Neurochirurgie, 1967; 2 items
  - Seven, M. J., 1963; 1 item
  - Sewall, Lee G., 1954; 1 item
  - Shaiova, Charles H., 1948-1952; 22 items
  - Shakow, David, 1949-1952; 3 items
  - Shamos, Morris H., 1967; 1 item
  - Shannon, Claude, 1949-1950; 9 items
  - Shapiro, Arthur, 1954; 1 item
  - Share, Isaiah A., 1950-1952; 7 items
  - Share, Si, 1953; 1 item
  - Sharp, Mrs. Martha, 1957; 1 item